レベルの高いサバイバルバトルが 繰り広げられるようになる フロアマスターへの挑戦権を懸けた 試合へと変わり ２００階クラスからは この闘技場の最高位 ここは　戦いを望む者にとって 最高の舞台なのだ １００階クラスからは 専用の個室が与えられる 高さ９９１ｍを誇る　この建物は 地上２５１階 天空闘技場 その階層に見合った報酬が 得られ 試合に勝てば 上の階へとクラスが上がり 格闘家の聖地である
Been a while since I flipped my switch on.
今日　キルアちゃんに勝って ６勝
has learned of the Chimera Ants
from the biological survey team, and now awaits the world leaders'
decision on how to handle them.
そして　あと３回　同じような カモを見つけて勝てば…
We're counting on you.
ヘッヘッヘ　フロアマスターね。
You have a single mission.
それで　俺の一生の 富と名声が約束される。
The immediate extermination
of these dangerous creatures.
動くと殺す。
We will use any means necessary.
「念」を使うと殺す 声を出しても殺す。
Will that be acceptable?
分かったら　ゆっくり目を閉じろ。
Naturally, we have no intention of
telling the experts how to proceed.
約束を破ったらどうなるか 分かったか？ 分かったら　ゆっくり目を開けて 鏡の俺を見て　よく聞け。
We simply desire those dangerous creatures
eradicated as swiftly as possible. Understood.
二度と俺達の前に 汚ねぇ面　出すな。
So their goal is to eradicate the Ants,
leaving the Hunters Association
約束だぜ。
to take the blame.
姑息な手段を使ってでも フロアマスターに しがみつこうとする　やから達
have five ranks, w-with the Queen at the top.
「念」に磨きをかけ さらなる強さを目指すゴンは
Queen
今宵　サダソ戦の時を迎える
There's the Queen. Royal Guard
あいつは
Under her is the Royal Guard, Squadron Leaders and then, the Squadron Leaders.
あれは闇の世界で 生きている奴の目だね。 絶望的だったね 目が合った瞬間に
Under the Squadron Leaders are Captains, and they oversee many foot
soldiers and other grunts.
自分が食われる立場の 生き物だと 思い知らされるほど 力の差を感じた。
A-And once the King is born,
the hierarchy shifts like so.
あいつを子供だと思って 侮ったのが そもそもの間違いだったね。
The Royal Guard that followed the Queen switches into the King's service.
俺は消える 殺されたくないからね。 気をつけろよ 次は　きっと　お前達ね。
A-Afterwards, Squadron Leaders
report directly to the Queen, and she focuses on directing the soldiers.
[TEL]
The Queen remains in the castle,
periodically giving birth to Kings.
どうする？ 俺は　やるぜ どんな汚いてを使ってもな…。
The Kings travel and mate
with different organisms, so as to breed new Queens.
フロアマスターは目の前だ！
That explains their fast reproduction rate.
２００階クラスで　１０勝すれば 晴れて　フロアマスターに 挑戦できる。
To prevent a Chimera Ant population explosion, you must defeat the Queen before
she can give birth to a King.
そこで勝てば ワンフロア　丸々 専有できるんだぜ。 うっ　ううう…。
But first, you need to defeat
all the soldiers guarding her.
そして　フロアマスターの 称号さえあれば
That's a tall order.
あのガキに また　脅されたりしないかな？
Got it. We'll be waiting.
あいつは　まだ 俺の能力を知らない。
The punitive force's first wave is on its way.
慎重に行動すれば　決して 対処できない相手じゃないさ。
Punitive force? I wonder who they'll send.
違うね
They'll be facing those vicious Chimera Ants.
あんたの能力なんて関係ない。
They'll be strong. They'd better be!
ゲゲっ！
I'm worried about Kite and the kids.
単に忠告なら いつでもできると思っただけさ。
They'll arrive in three days.
クソしてる時でも…　ね。
How?
言っておくぜ ルールは守れよ。
There must have been some catalyst. A catalyst...
結局　得するのは 俺達なんだぜ。
Rock... Paper...
フフっ。
Damn...
やっぱり 悪いことをしちゃあ　いけないな。 正々堂々と戦おう！ うん。
What if their attacks were the catalyst?
サダソ選手　時間切れ 不戦勝　ゴン選手！
I told you that we are capable
of anything that humans are.
え　またかよ！
Including the use of this strange power?
サダソの野郎 何やってんだ！
But this is...
さて　今日の試合 ゴンくんは　ギドと
Then I won't hold back.
キルアくんはリールベルトとの 対戦が組まれていますが
Come.
何か対策は　ありますか？ うん　えと　ウイングさん 実はね…。
Colt! This is a message from Hagya.
なるほど。
This is a message from Hagya.
さぁ　いよいよ注目の リベンジマッチが始まります。 ギド選手　ｖｓ　ゴン選手！
The ultimate prey is either
within the factory or nearby.
前回の対戦で病院送りにされた ゴン選手は　どう戦うのか？
Capture it.
今日は　なんと 釣り竿を持っての登場です！
Capture it...
どんな戦い方を 見せてくれるのか？
Dead or alive.
試合開始です！
Capture it!
おっと　開始早々 ゴン選手　猛ダッシュ！
Hagya-sama... What is it? Do you believe they will succeed?
あっ！　しかし　ギド選手も それを予期していたか
There are enough Captains for a decent fight.
しょっぱなから 「竜巻独楽」で応戦。
For a decent fight, huh?
ここに　ただ　突っ込んで行っては 前回の　二の舞いです。
But I doubt they'll be much help.
やっぱり読まれてたか
I'm fine with that. Why is that?
ヒッヒッヒ… お前の考えなど　お見通しよ
They're just buying time for us to arrive.
一度　回り始めたら 俺を止めるのは至難
Oh, I see.
そこで　誰もが回り始める前に 攻撃と考えるからな
Then the rare humans will be ours to take.
どうした！　そっちが来ないなら 俺から行くぞ！
Exactly.
見たかよ　今の…。 すげぇ。
We're surrounded.
あいつも 相当　怒ってるってことだな
Now, then... Let's decide order and methodology.
ズシを利用されたことに 今度は俺の番だ！ さぁ　ゴン選手 一体　どんな技を使うのか？
As for our targets, you have three choices. One...
釣り竿による攻撃 考えられるのは
Decide the order in which you will fight.
釣り針を俺の体の一部に 引っ掛けて回転を止める
Two, attempt to escape. Three, give up and let us capture you.
だが　そう　うまく行くかな？
If you choose option one, you will fight one-on-one battles with us
行った！ ギド選手めがけて一直線！
I don't recommend the second option.
ヒッヒッヒ　やはりか だが無駄だ！
You'll anger us, resulting in a brutal capture and prolonged suffering for all of you.
ヒッヒッヒ　どこを狙っている。 えいっ！
That would anger us even more than option two.
おりゃ！ 何!?
So, what will you do?
なんと！　リングの石板ごと ギド選手をひっくり返した！
Kite... We couldn't have asked for a better deal.
うわ　うわ！
One-on-one fights with their Captains.
うぅ…。
We'll start with whoever is prepared to fight. I'll go.
うぅ…！
No, I will.
うぅ　うぅ…！ ふん！
First comes rock! Rock, paper, scissors!
そっちが　どんなてでも使うなら こっちも同じだ。 もう一度　ズシに手を出してみろ。 次は全力で　その顔をぶっ飛ばす！
While the Ants have inherited
individualism from humans, they've lost the unity that's
characteristic of ants. I hope we'll be able
勝者　ゴン選手！
Well, we need to decide who
to send from our side.
ゴン選手　見事な勝利で 雪辱を果たしました！
#6... #6!
これで２００階クラスでの成績は ２勝１敗！
Who's #6?
さて　俺の番だな。
Whoever dies first loses.
さぁ　続きましては 本日のメーンイベント
We can't just surrender? What?!
サダソ戦　不戦勝の キルア選手にとっては
Are you crazy?
この試合が２００階クラスの 実質的な初戦。 一体　どんな戦いを 見せてくれるのでしょうか？
If you lose, we'll feed you to the Queen. If you don't defeat me,
you're guaranteed to die!
約束を守らなかったのは そっちだから もう　負けてやんないぜ。
Yeah, I'm okay with that. But there's no need for you to die. If I beat you, I won't want to eat you.
((あれは　闇の世界で 生きている奴の目だね))
If you surrender, you'll live.
闇の世界の住人か…
But if you lose, you must promise never to eat another human.
このガキが　いくら その道のプロでも
This guy isn't taking us seriously!
天空闘技場は　俺の土俵だ
He has more pep than any human I've seen!
この四角いリングの上なら 俺のほうが上だってことを
Lucky you, Baro-chan!
思い知らせてやる！
I'll kill you!
ポイント＆ノックアウト制 時間無制限
Then how about this?
始め！
The same attack?
「オーラバースト」！
Gon!
おっと！ 猛ダッシュで危機を回避！ 溜めたオーラを一気に噴出することで 得た推進力を利用し
I'm fine.
自在に車椅子を操ります！ 跳び過ぎちった
Why are you so tough? By this point, the rest were vomiting organs.
ふぅ…　ヤバい　ヤバい
Whatever...
「ツインスネイク」！
There's no way to dodge my homing roll!
出ました！ 「ソング　オブ　ディフェンス」！
What will you do, Gon?
すさまじいスピードで　うねる ２本のムチは 完璧に自身を守りつつ
Kid, I have something to
tell you before I kill you.
攻撃の機をうかがうかのように 間合いを詰める！
The main reason we kill humans isn't to eat them
フン！　奇襲で先手を とるつもりだったんだろうが
or to feed them to the Queen. Then why?
残念だったな。
Because it's fun!
この型に持ち込めば もはや　お前に勝機はない。 何で？ 見れば分かるだろう。
I love the sound as humans
vomit their own organs with a plop!
常人に　このムチの動きを 見切ることは不可能！
It's hilarious because it looks like barf.
狭いリングの上では 逃げも隠れもできんぞ。
That isn't funny. I'll make you vomit your own
organs with a plop, too!
だが！
He didn't dodge...
あっ　うっ　あぁ…！
Compared to Razor's spikes, this is nothing!
どんな大男でも 身動きすらできずに気を失う。 ムチに逆らうバカどもは
Well, we're in a hurry.
全て　この「サンダースネイク」の 餌食とな…。
Who's my opponent?
あ…!!
Hey!
拷問の訓練で電流は慣れっこさ 俺には効かない。
#3. #3's up!
でも　効かないってのは 我慢できるって意味でさ
You won't be smiling for long. I'm about to show you hell.
痛いことには 変わりないんだよね。
Got it?
だから　ちょっと頭来た。
I'm nothing like the trash over there. Trash?
ヒッ！ その高さから床に激突したら 死ぬなぁ！
Huh? I said trash because he's trash.
どうする？ 頼む！　受け止めてくれ！
I'm ten times stronger than that guy.
ＯＫ　安心して落ちて来な！
Oh, that's nothing to brag about. What was that?!
うわ！ あ!!
When they enter battle,
their aura becomes much stronger. They're at their best in battle.
ったく　どんだけ痛いか分かったか バカ！
Gon tends to have an agitatingly slow start, but we should have time.
リールベルト選手 失神によるＫＯと見なし 勝者　キルア選手！
We'll reach the Queen before
she gives birth to the King. But why
わぁ　ハハっ！　うわ！
do I have such a bad feeling?
ナイス　キルア。
There's a gnawing anxiety that won't go away.
次は　ゴンの番だぜ ６日後だったな　奴とやるの。
Look, Peggy!
うん　６月１０日。 さっきのは　俺以外じゃ できない勝ち方だからな。
I can freely control this energy!
あの電気ムチは 一度でも食らったら いくら　お前でも 気　失っちゃうぜ。
This is incredible!
うん。
We should do more research.
どう戦う？
Eh?
大丈夫　ては考えた。 ふん。
If we learn the proper way
to wield this power, we can synchronize it with our natural abilities
見ながら　ちゃんと戦ってたか
to make it an even stronger weapon.
やっぱり　お前も実戦派だな
You're too retentive...
ギド選手は　やはり 先日のゴン選手との戦いで 受けたダメージが大きく
Find and secure him.
ご存じのように ４敗すると即失格。 またイチから やり直さなくてはなりません。
My entire body is covered by hardened skin.
今日は　ゴン選手の 素早さを警戒してか 初めから ムチを手にしております。
I can take as many of those
attacks as you can throw! Oh, yeah?
おっ!? おりゃ！
Is there anyone ten times
stronger than this guy?
なんと！　今度は素手で 石板を引っぺがした！
This is a pleasant surprise.
ん　そりゃ！
Their Captains can be dispatched easily enough.
そんでもって　投げた！ 「オーラバースト」！
Am I worried over nothing?
うお！　辛うじて脱出！
That's enough... It's my turn!
わざと逃げ道を残したな
2!
あっ！ おっと　しかし　ゴン選手 予想していたかのごとく 先回り！
What?
逃げなきゃならない この場面
Two, huh?
方向転換している暇が ないから
Damn, bad spin. Killua...
前方に進むしかない
That scythe is nasty.
しかも急激なダッシュによって 体のバランスも崩れ
Gon, Killua...
どうしても　一瞬ムチの動きは 止まらざるを得ない
In three seconds, jump up.
そこを捕らえる ヘヘっ！
Wh-What is this overwhelming pressure?
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。 あっ…。
I've experienced this sensation before!
これがスイッチか えっと　出力を最大にして。
Silent Waltz: Grim Reaper's Dance
何ちゃって…　ベェ。
I remember now.
リールベルト選手 失神ＫＯと見なし
This is
勝者　ゴン選手！
death!
ゴンさん！ アハハハ。
Murder via overwhelming force.
いや　お見事。
So why did you choose that power?
前の戦いを含め　十分及第だ。
Be cautious as we advance. As I mentioned, that won't be
enough to kill them immediately.
場所　日時ともに　君が決めていい。
Are you okay?
いつでも相手になるよ。
It's only getting worse from here. If you start to sympathize with the enemy,
you won't be able to handle what's coming.
これまでのゴンの戦いに その実力を認めたヒソカ
What would you do if one of those
bugs cared for its comrades?
２人の戦いは いよいよ間近に迫っていた
Kite, Gon, and Killua head toward
the Chimera Ant Queen's castle